vitadigest.com 2008-06-08

# VitaDigest - The Vitamins Supplement and Sports Nutrition SuperStore - 1-877-848-2168 Privacy Policy

| | |   
---|---|---  
**WELCOME TO VITADIGEST.COM** [](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.vitadigest.com&sealid=101)

****PRIVACY POLICY****

At Vitadigest.com, your privacy is our top priority. Please read our privacy policy details. This privacy statement discloses the privacy and security practices for Vitadigest.com website.

 **Overview**   
Our Internet Superstore allows you to buy products and services, receive special discounts, fill out surveys, and receive e-mails or other promotional information from us. We use the information that we collect about you to fulfill your product and service purchases and to create a more personalized online experience. This is just a brief overview, so please read on for more details about our Privacy Policy. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically. Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you online. We encourage you to ask questions and to be very cautious before you disclose your personal information to others.

 **Truste Licensee**

Vitadigest.com is a licensee of TRUSTe. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because Vitadigest.com wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. By displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, this website has agreed to explain the following regarding the use of our site:

 **1.** What information does vitadigest.com collect from you?   
**2.** Where do we collect information from you and how do we use it?   
**3.** Who is collecting your information?   
**4.** With whom do we share your information?   
**5.** What are your choices regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?   
**6.** What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?    
**7.** A special note about children’s privacy.   
**8.** Vitadigest.com and third-party use of “cookies and action tags".   
**9.** What types of Credit Card Security vitadigest.com have?   
**10.** Vitadigest.com commitment to you.   
**11.** Contacting vitadigest.com about privacy questions or concerns.

Questions regarding this Policy should be directed to [privacy@vitadigest.com](mailto:privacy@vitadigest.com:) or may also be contacted directly at the following address: 

Attn: Privacy Compliance Officer   
VITADIGEST.COM, Inc.   
20687-2 Amar Rd. #258   
Walnut CA 91789
If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or it is not satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe through the TRUSTe Watchdog Dispute Resolution Process http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php. TRUSTe will serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve users concerns. 

* * *

************1\. What information does vitadigest.com collect from you?****

In order to better provide you with numerous products and services, vitadigest.com collects two types of information about its visitors: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our site. Your phone number is used only in the event that our customer service representatives need to contact you about an order you have placed.

 **Personally Identifiable Information**   
This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. Personal information is requested when you order a product or service, fill out surveys, and send us feedback. For example, this information might include your name, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card or other payment information, and product details. With this information, vitadigest.com can fill your orders and better provide you with personalized services.

 **Non-Personally Identifiable Information**   
This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you shop on our site in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. For example, this information may include the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. A URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol ("TCP/IP") network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks like the Web use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet, browse and shop. 

* * *

************2\. Where do we collect information from you and how do we use it?****

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide vitadigest.com's visitors with a superior customized online experience. We use the customer contact information to fill orders, contact purchasers to inform them of their order status, to send promotional information, to enhance the operation of our site and administer our systems.

We gather information in the following ways:

 **Shopping**   
We collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to gather broad demographic information, to enable ads to be served on our site, to report Non-Personally Identifiable Information to our advertisers, and to monitor the level of activity on our site. We collect information from visitors to our site regarding the URLs they came from, domain types (e.g., .com or .org), their IP addresses, the date and time of their visit or order, the number of visits and orders, the number of visits per browsing session, the server type, the operating system and browser type used to come to the site, the country, state and telephone area code where their servers are located, the pages and page titles of our site that visitors viewed during their visit, whether the visitor's computer is enabled for Java or cookies, browser language, applications and plug-ins, and any search terms entered on our site.

 **Ordering**   
When you order from us, we collect personally identifiable information from you. If you order one of our products or services, we will collect and maintain your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, product selections, credit card or other payment information, order number, referring URL, IP address, page you bought from. We collect this, and other information, as disclosed in this Policy, in order to fill your order, to communicate with you about your order and to send you promotional materials. Before confirming your order, you will have the opportunity to review the product order form and make changes and additions to the information it contained and these changes will be automatically kept for future use.

 **Online Surveys and Polling**   
In order to improve our services to you, we ask some of our customers to voluntarily complete surveys, which may be collected by an independent third party. Individual survey answers are confidential, although Non-Personally Identifiable Information is collected and disclosed to third parties. If you do not wish to participate in a survey, simply decline to participate when asked.

 **Newsletters & Promotional E-mails**   
We offer free newsletters, such as our vitadigest.com promotional e-mails as a service to our customers. We will send you newsletters and e-mails periodically listing current specials and deals. To stop receiving our newsletter, send an e-mail to us at optout@vitadigest.com.

 **Contact Information**   
If you contact us by calling one of our customer service representatives, we may ask for your name, e-mail address and order information in order to send you a reply. We may keep a record of your correspondence or comments. If you report a problem with our site, we may collect such information in a file specific to you.

 **Affiliate Program**   
Our Affiliate Program (Affiliate Connection) is administered by a third party, on a third party's Web site. Any information collected by them is not governed by this Policy.

 **Advertising**   
We may display advertisements on our site. By knowing a little about you, vitadigest.com will be able to deliver more relevant advertisements and content to you in the form of targeted banners and promotions. For example, advertisers give us an advertisement and tell us the type of audience they want to reach (e.g., buyers of Xenadrine). Vitadigest.com takes the advertisement and includes it in a vitadigest.com e-mail to prior customers meeting that criterion.

We also track customers' traffic patterns throughout their online session, including which pages, information and advertisements a customer views while using the site and what items they place in their basket or purchase. We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our servers, software, to administer our site and to gather demographic information.

We may share aggregated statistics about pages viewed on our site, sales and other shopping information with third parties. 

* * *

************3\. Who is collecting your information?****

 **Ad Servers and Content Servers:** We may use third party ad servers or content servers to serve ads, product information, or other information both on and off our site. Those third parties may use "action tags" or web beacons throughout the site to count the number of visitors who click on a banner ad or other information and to track the number of customers who continue on to make a purchase. They may also place their own "cookie" on your computer to help those ads to run and analyze site usage. We do not provide them with any of your Personally Identifiable Information.

 **E-mail Services:** We use a third party to send promotional e-mails to customers. Images contained in the email may be served by the third party. They collect certain information about you such as your IP address, browser type, your operating system, the time and date that a particular email was viewed, and whether you responded to a particular ad or email, products viewed and whether you continued on to make a purchase. They may use a "cookie" or "action tags."

 **Website Analysis Agent:** We may contract with several online partners to help manage and optimize our Internet business and marketing. We use the services of marketing companies to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site. To do this, we use Action Tags and cookies provided by the marketing companies on this site. The type of information we collect includes things such as pages, information and advertisements viewed as well as what items are placed in a shopping basket or purchased, the order number, the amount of a purchase, the product number and the quantity purchased. By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn things like what kinds of customers our site attracts, which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. Although the marketing companies log the information coming from our site on our behalf, we control how the data may and may not be used.

On occasion, unaffiliated third parties will "frame" vitadigest.com's site in an effort to collect customer information. To ensure your privacy, make sure that your order originates from vitadigest.com's site. Vitadigest.com is not in any manner responsible in the event that you do disclose information to an unaffiliated framing site.

 **Email to A Friend Function**   
The Email to A Friend Function is a uniquely design function that intend to provide our customer the ability to recommend our product to friends or family members.

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send the friend a **one-time** email inviting them to visit our site. VitaDigest.com **do not store** this information. The emails are for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. All E-mail provided would never be collect or use for any other purpose.

 **Live Help Option**   
Live help option is a tools that provide our customer an instant customer service. With this tool Customer will be able to ask question and directly interact with our customer service representative. All information transfer through Live Help will never be recorded nor use for any other purpose. **All Chat are One on One bases.**

* * *

************4\. With whom do we share your information?****

 **Fulfillment:** The information collected by vitadigest.com is used for processing orders, keeping you informed about your order status, for statistical purposes, for improving our site and its performance, to serve ads, and to notify you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you. We will disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties to charge your credit card, fill your order, and deliver your order. For example, we must release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment; and release your address and telephone information to the delivery service to deliver products that you ordered.

 **Other Parties:** We do not sell, trade, or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to others without your consent. We may provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our customers' sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to third parties, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information. We may release account information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions or to protect the rights, property, and safety of vitadigest.com, our users, or others. If customers do not pay us for products ordered, we may submit their account information to a third party collection agency.

 **Services Provided on Our Site:** Except as otherwise stated in this Policy, without your consent, vitadigest.com does not disclose its customers' Personally Identifiable Information to other merchants.

 **Compliance with Service of Process or Law Enforcement:** Occasionally vitadigest.com may be asked by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation, without prior notice to you. Vitadigest.com fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we believe to be unlawful. We tried very hard to work with law enforcement authorities to investigate and prosecute the fraudulent use of credit cards. Our system automatically verifies all addresses with VISA, MasterCard, Discover and American Express. Your IP address will be automatically recorded as part of your order. **All fraudulent activities will be reported directly to FBI.** **Every order that is made over $300, our company requires a signed authorization form which should be filled out by the card holder, and fax us back in order for us to process the order. 

* * *

************5\. What are your choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information?****

 **Email:** We may from time to time send you e-mail or other communications regarding current promotions, specials and new additions to the vitadigest.com site. You may "opt-out," or unsubscribe from our newsletters by following the unsubscribe instructions in any e-mail you receive from us, or by sending an e-mail to optout@vitadigest.com. After doing so, vitadigest.com users will not receive future promotional emails unless they sign up to receive newsletters or emails.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If, however, we are going to use users personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users **via email** and/or **by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days**

* * *

************6\. What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?****

In order to most efficiently serve you, credit card transactions and order fulfillment are handled by established third party banking, processing agents and distribution institutions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process and ship your order.

When you access your account information, the information is kept on a secure server. All of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access by physical security means. 

* * *

************7\. A special note about children's privacy****

Because of the nature of the World Wide Web, Vitadigest.com cannot prohibit minors from visiting this site. Vitadigest.com must rely on parents, guardians and those responsible for supervising children and teenagers to decide which materials are appropriate for such children and teenagers to view and/or purchase. Vitadigest.com requires that (i) all purchases on the site be made by adults 18 years of age or older, and (ii) all users who provide personal information to Vitadigest.com must be 18 years of age or older. 

* * *

************8\. Vitadigest.com and third-party use of "cookies" and "action tags."****

 **Vitadigest.com Cookies:** When you use our site we will store cookies on your computer in order to facilitate and customize your use of our site. A cookie is a small data text file, which a Web site stores on your computer's hard drive (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to vitadigest.com. Web sites create cookies to record information about your preferences, such as the items you add to your shopping cart and make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site. Most cookies expire after a certain time period. Our cookies store randomly assigned user identification numbers, and your first name to welcome you back to our site. The most popular browsers, such as Netscape Navigator and Internet Explorer, can be set to give you the option of accepting or rejecting all cookies.

 **Action Tags, Web Beacons and other Data Collection Methods:** An action tag or a web-beacon (also known as a clear gif or a pixel tag) is a method used to track responses or actions by customers who view certain advertisements or other information on our site. Action tags are 1x1 pixel images embedded in a website page that are used to transparently collect information. Our website analysis agents may use action tags to count the number of times that visitors click on a particular banner ad or visit the pages of our site and to provide information about what products are viewed or purchased. Without collecting any personally identifiable information, they use that data to tell us (and other advertisers) which ads are the most effective on particular sites. Our website analysis agents may use an action tag on our checkout page, and other pages, to keep anonymous track of the number of times that clicking on a banner ad or views other information on our site results in a purchase. They also collect the amount of the purchase, order confirmation number, quantity and identity of product purchased.

 **E-mail Distributor's Use of Action Tags:** Our third-party e-mail distributor may also use action tags. They may, for example, keep track of when a promotional e-mail is opened and provide vitadigest.com with ongoing aggregated reports of how many customers have responded. We share with them web site usage information about visitors to our web site who have received a promotional e-mail or other targeted promotional campaign. They use the information for the purpose of targeting future campaigns. 

* * *

************9\. What types of Credit Card Security vitadigest.com have? ****

The Internet is a vast network of computers. Because the data passes from computer to computer, some Internet shoppers worry that unauthorized persons may intercept the data and gain access to credit card numbers, but shopping on a secure site is actually safer than handing a credit card to a waiter in a restaurant. Taking the steps below will lower the chances of interception of your credit card number:

* Limit your online shopping to Internet merchants, such as Vitadigest.com, with sites equipped with Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL prevents unauthorized people from intercepting your data.
* Use a browser, such as Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer that supports SSL. These browsers show a symbol in the status bar, such as a key or lock, when you are on a site that uses SSL. Most banks will cover the cost of fraud resulting from unauthorized use of your credit card or may limit your liability.

Credit card information collected by Vitadigest.com is encrypted through Secure Sockets Layer before it is transmitted over the Internet. 

* * *

************10\. Vitadigest.com commitment to you.****

Your privacy is importance to us. It is our goal to run an efficient, friendly business that is quick and most importantly safe. As pointed out above, everything done on Vitadigest.com is secure and your information is completely confidential. 

* * *

************11\. Contacting vitadigest.com about privacy questions or concerns.****

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact vitadigest.com by sending a letter to: 

Attn: Privacy Compliance Officer   
VITADIGEST.COM, Inc.   
20687-2 Amar Rd. #258   
Walnut CA 91789
You may also contact us by e-mail at [privacy@vitadigest.com](mailto:privacy@vitadigest.com)

Last Updated: 10/24/2006

Back to Top

 _This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._
